[{"question": "  i just walked in the bathroom and saw kathy naked! it was like torture!", "answer": " y'know if we ever go to war and you\u0092re captured, you\u0092re in for a big surprise.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " wow! could everyone totally see up his robe?", "answer": " yeah! oh my god! opening credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " here you go.", "answer": " great! all right, so i\u0092ll call you later.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": "  hey-hey-hey! who was that?", "answer": " that would be casey. we\u0092re going out tonight.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " goin\u0092 out, huh? wow! wow!  so things didn\u0092t work out with kathy, huh? bummer.", "answer": " no, things are fine with kathy. i\u0092m having a late dinner with her tonight, right after my early dinner with casey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 13, "asentId": 14}, {"question": "  what?", "answer": " yeah-yeah. and the craziest thing is that i just ate a whole pizza by myself!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " wait! you\u0092re going out with kathy!", "answer": " yeah. why are you getting so upset?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " what is the big deal? it\u0092s not like we\u0092re exclusive.", "answer": " look, joey, kathy is clearly not fulfilling your emotional needs. but casey, i mean granted i only saw the back of her head, but i got this sense that she\u0092s-she\u0092s smart, and funny, and gets you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " you got all that from the back of her head?", "answer": " all right look, i think it\u0092s time for you to settle down. y'know? make a choice, pick a lane.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": "  \"little, tiny tarzan, swinging on a nose hair. swinging with the greatest of ease\u009a\" darn it! now, i don\u0092t know who to get to the next verse.", "answer": " oh, you could just go uh, \"greatest of ease\u009a  bah-bah-bha-bhannn.\" then go right into it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " yeah, ooh, i like that! yeah. wait! how do you know about \u0091bah-bah-bha-bhan?\u0092", "answer": " well umm, y\u0092know, i used to play.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " oh yeah, that\u0092s right, the keyboards, huh?", "answer": " yeah, just a little in high school, but then i really got into it in college. i mean that\u0092s-that\u0092s when i really found my sound.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " oh god! orange juice just came out of my nose, but it was totally worth it. oh my god, i completely forgot about your sound.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " he used to lock himself in the basement for hours. no one was every allowed to hear, \"the sound.\"", "answer": " i wanna hear \"the sound.\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " really? no. i mean, nah, i haven\u0092t played in so long, and-and, well it\u0092s-it\u0092s really personal stuff, y\u0092know?", "answer": " come on, play that funky music white boy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " no, you guys, i mean my keyboards are all the way up in\u0097no, yeah, okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " okay, guys.", "answer": " all right! bring it on, you\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " here we go.  y\u0092know, i\u0092ve-i\u0092ve never played my stuff for anyone before, so it\u0092s important that-that you understand it\u0092s about communicating very private emotions.  y\u0092know, umm, you should-you should think of umm, my work as wordless sound poems. that\u0092s what i\u0092m\u009a", "answer": "  oh my god! play!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": "  boy, that was-that was, umm\u009a terrific.", "answer": " really, bitchin\u0092!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " wow, it was so\u0097wow!", "answer": " really?! i mean, really?!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " yeah, i mean, you should play in public!", "answer": " wow! thanks, you guys. that\u0092s uh\u0097ohhh, i wanna, i wanna play you another piece! umm! uh-oh! i left my uh, helicopter sounds on another disk. i\u0092ll be right back! okay?  this is so nice, i\u0092m\u0097i am so\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " oh god bless my dad sound proofing the basement!", "answer": " oh, i can\u0092t believe i ever let him touch me with those fingers.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " what are you guys talking about, i loved it! it was soo moving. oh, plus it\u0092s just, it\u0092s so different from the stuff you usually hear.", "answer": " you mean like, music?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " come in!", "answer": "  hey!  oh god, is that baywatch?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " uh yes, but uh, i just watch it for the articles.", "answer": " so is joey around?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " no-no, he\u0092s not back yet, but he\u0092ll be here any minute. so uh, come on in. have a seat. bow or stern?", "answer": " i uh, don\u0092t really have a preference. you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " i like it in the stern.  \u009aof the boat.   hello.", "answer": "  hey, it\u0092s me. listen casey and i were on our way back and had a little car trouble.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " what happened?", "answer": " we broke down on the parkway, so i have to walk back and get some transmission fluid. and hey, listen could you please tell kathy that i\u0092ll be there as soon as i can.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": " why can\u0092t you tell her?", "answer": " \u0091cause i only have one quarter, and i think my time is about to\u0097", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " joey! joey!!", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " i thought your time ran out.", "answer": " me too, but i guess i do have a couple of more\u0097", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": "  uhh, that was joey. he\u0092s running a little late, he says he\u0092s sorry.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " so i guess it\u0092s just uh, you and me then.", "answer": " oh, okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " yeah, i think it is!", "answer": " so what did you do today?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " oh, i had an appointment to get my haircut\u009a", "answer": "  oh, it looks great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " \u009aand then it got canceled.", "answer": " well, i could cut it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " really?! you do that?", "answer": " yeah, i do. of course, i learned at my aunt\u0092s dog grooming shop, but hey, what do you say?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " you have really great hair.", "answer": " well, thanks. i grow it myself.  y\u0092know who also has great hair is joey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " what-what \u0091cha doin\u0092?", "answer": " checking to see if it\u0092s even.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " \u0091kay.", "answer": " looks good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": "  oh the phone! the phone\u0092s making sounds!  hello!", "answer": "  hey dude, it\u0092s me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " hey it\u0092s joey!", "answer": " listen uh, i\u0092m really sorry, it looks like i\u0092m gonna be stuck here for a while. i got the transmission fluid, but when i went to put it in the car, the transmission wasn\u0092t there!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " yeah, it must\u0092ve fallen out a few blocks back. i just figured we hit a dog.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " listen uh, could you put kathy on, i wanna apologize.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": "  hey.  oh no it\u0092s fine, don\u0092t worry about it.  yeah-no, stop apologizing, it\u0092s okay.  yeah! i\u0092ll talk to you tomorrow.   i should uh, probably go.", "answer": " yeah. yes! yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " i forgot my purse.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " no-no-no-no, this is bad! it\u0092s bad! this is bad!", "answer": " horrible!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " wait the uh, the kiss or the situation?", "answer": " no-no-no, the kiss was good.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " okay!", "answer": " no, but that\u0092s bad!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " ooh! yes! okay! here\u0092s what we do, we-we forget it happened.", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " okay, we-we swallow our feelings. even if it means we\u0092re unhappy forever. sound good?", "answer": " can you really do that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " i have to; he\u0092s my best friend, and you\u0092re seeing him.", "answer": " chandler, i like joey a lot, but with you\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": "  oh-no-no-no! don\u0092t! don\u0092t! see-see, you\u0092re getting me confused, i\u0092m starting to urn.", "answer": " i\u0092m sorry. if you wanna pretend that nothing happened, i can try.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " i-i think we have too.", "answer": " okay. bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " bye.  are you still out there?", "answer": "  no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": "  electrifying.  emphatic time-time-time\u009a", "answer": "  y'know, there\u0092s a starbucks about three blocks down.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": "  thank you guys-guys-guys\u009a", "answer": "  hey, aren\u0092t you up next?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " oh no, i\u0092m not playing tonight.", "answer": " why not?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " i can\u0092t follow ross! it\u0092d be like those bicycle ridding chimps that followed the beetles. no.", "answer": " phoebe, ross sucks!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " phoebe, the place has emptied because of him.", "answer": " oh my god, he\u0092s not even appreciated in his own time. i would give anything to not be appreciated in my own time!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " okay. umm, phoebe, you suck too.", "answer": " yeah, phoebe you\u0092re\u009a awful!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": "  oh my god! what happened here? did you do all this?", "answer": " i sure did.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " why?", "answer": " well, i just thought it\u0092d make me feel good to do something nice for my friend.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " well, you\u0092re amazing.", "answer": " oh no-no-no. this is amazing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": "  a tv as if it appears from nowhere! that\u0092s the dream! man, how did you afford this stuff?", "answer": " well, y\u0092know i\u0092m 29. i mean who needs a savings account.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " oh, you are the best friends anyone has ever had.", "answer": " oh, i don\u0092t know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " oh-no-no-no, you are! you do this, you give me the great advice, and hey listen, i was thinking about what you said yesterday about focusing on one woman, i\u0092m gonna do that.", "answer": " you mean with casey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " no-no-no, i think i\u0092m gonna see how things go with kathy. she\u0092s pretty cool.", "answer": " or casey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " no-no, kathy.", "answer": " could be casey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " no. no, kathy.", "answer": " consider casey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " y\u0092know what i think? i think somebody\u0092s got a little crush on casey. how \u0091bout i fix you two up? what do you think?", "answer": " that all the pieces of my life are falling right into place!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey! you were really great! you were really, really great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " oh, thanks, thanks. so monica tells me that uh, you don\u0092t want to play anymore because me and y'know my talent. is that true?", "answer": " well, kinda. yeah. yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " pheebs\u009a", "answer": " yeah, i-i can\u0092t\u0097i mean y\u0092know i was trying to be really y'know okay and upbeat about it, i just\u0097i feel so dwarfed by your musical gift.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " see but, pheebs that-that is the exact opposite intent of my music. y\u0092know my music is-is meant to inspire, and if it bothers you this much, then i\u009a i won\u0092t play anymore.", "answer": " oh no. no-no-no, don\u0092t do that! how could i live with myself if i knew i was depriving the world of your music.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " hey chandler! saw the new furniture. very nice.", "answer": " yeah! joey has the best boyfriend ever!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " i kissed kathy.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " are you serious?", "answer": " does joey know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " no. is there anyway, anyway you think he\u0092ll understand this?", "answer": " you obviously haven\u0092t screwed over a lot of your friends.  which we all appreciate.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " no the-the sad thing is, if you had told him how you felt before you kissed her, knowing joey, he probably just would\u0092ve just stepped aside.", "answer": " oh, don\u0092t say that! don\u0092t say that. that\u0092s not true. is", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " i think maybe, yeah.", "answer": " he loves you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " then why didn\u0092t you tell me to do that?!!", "answer": " well, i said-i said something to phoebe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " yeah! no, that\u0092s right. and i thought it was a really good idea.", "answer": " i know, i remember that!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " i remember you did.", "answer": " god!!  what am i gonna do?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " well, chandler, you\u0092re gonna have to tell him.", "answer": " why?! why do i have to tell him?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " because you do.", "answer": " yeah, i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey! samboucha margarita?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " is that a real thing?", "answer": " well, we only had samboucha, so it is now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " listen ah, joe, i-i need to, i need to talk to you about something.", "answer": " what\u0092s up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " it\u0092s-it\u0092s about kathy. umm, uh, i like her. i like her a lot actually.", "answer": " you do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " well, you\u0092re timing couldn\u0092t be better. she\u0092s not my girlfriend anymore.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " what?", "answer": " yeah, she broke up with me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " oh uh, when?", "answer": " just now, after acting class. at first i thought she was doing some kind of scene, that\u0092s why i let people watch.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " oh man, i am so sorry. are, are you okay?", "answer": " well, i\u0092ve been better. but, i\u0092m all right. so you like her huh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " yes, but i-i uh, don\u0092t have too.", "answer": " no-no-no, no it\u0092s uh, it\u0092s okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " yeah?", "answer": " yeah. you know why? \u0091cause you can to me first.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " well, i thought that would be the best thing to do.", "answer": " but hey, listen just so you know, you might have you\u0092re work cut out for you. \u0091cause when i talked to her, i kinda got the feeling that she\u0092s into some other guy. so\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " see uh, that\u0092s-that\u0092s actually what i wanted to talk to you about. i-i think i know who the other guy is.", "answer": " who?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " it\u0092s me. i\u0092m the other guy.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " yeah, i mean when you were late last night, kathy and i got to talking, and one thing to another and\u009a", "answer": " and what?! did you sleep with her?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " no! no! no! i just kissed her.", "answer": " what?!! that\u0092s even worse!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " how is that worse?!", "answer": " i don\u0092t know! but it\u0092s the same!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " look, i\u0092m sorry! but there\u0092s nothing i can do, i think i\u0092m in love with her!", "answer": " who cares?! you went behind my back! i would never do that to you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " you\u0092re right, i have no excuses! i was totally over the line.", "answer": " over the line?! you-you\u0092re-you\u0092re so far past the line, that you-you can\u0092t even see the line! the line is a dot to you!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " yes. yes! right! and i feel horrible. you have to believe me!", "answer": " is that why you bought all this stuff?!  well, y\u0092know what i will not watch your tv, i will not listen to your stereo, and there\u0092s a cinnamon raisin loaf in the new bread maker that i\u0092m not gonna eat! you know why?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " probably because\u009a", "answer": " because it\u0092s all tainted with your betrayal. from now on this apartment is empty for me! and i\u0092m not happy about you either.  oh, and just so you know, i made that bread for you.  closing credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " oh my god, he\u0092s lost it. he\u0092s totally lost it.", "answer": "  what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " thank you, thanks.  yeah, i lost it. y\u0092know, i\u0092m not gonna play anymore,  would you, can you finish my set?", "answer": " after that? yeah! no, i mean if i can help.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " yeah, like i could lose it.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " okay, so you were trying to play bad this whole time.", "answer": " yeah\u0097no, just that last song.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep7.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}]